<resources>
    <string name="app_id">1065656899866</string>
    <string name="LEADERBOARD_ID">CgkImrLn8IEfEAIQAg</string>
    <string name="app_name">Magic Colors</string>
    <string name="signin_other_error">Error occurred</string>
    <string name="signin_failure">Could not signed in</string>

    //ENGLISH
    <string name="gametext_ing">GAME</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_ing">When the balls are down, you can touch any ball in any position.
        Whenever you touch a ball, you will receive 10 points, but the speed of the balls will increase. If you also want to get
        more points and make the speed of the balls decrease, you must do combos. After pressing the bonus ball, it does not matter
        Which ball touches, the combo will occur. If any ball reaches the end of the game screen, the game will end.
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_ing">COMBO</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_ing">Touch minimum 2 balls with the same color sequence</string>
    <string name="bonustext_ing">BONUS</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_ing"> Comes once in 15 moves and shift color</string>

    //TURKISH
    <string name="gametext_tr">OYUN</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_tr">Toplar aşağı doğru inerken istediğine basabilirsin. Her topa
        basışta puan toplarsın ancak topların hızı da artar.Eğer daha fazla puan kazanmak ve aynı zamanda
        hızın azalmasını istiyorsan combo yapmalısın.Ayrıca bonus topundan sonra herhangi bir topa bastığında combo olur.
        Top ekranın sonuna varırsa oyun biter.
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_tr">KOMBO</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_tr"> Ard arda aynı renkte en az 2 topa basmak.</string>
    <string name="bonustext_tr">BONUS</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_tr">Her 15 basışta bir gelen ve renk değiştiren top.</string>

    //CHİNA
    <string name="gametext_ch">游戏</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_ch">
当球下来时，你可以接触任何球
        位置。每当你触摸一个球，你会得到10分，但球的速度增加。
        如果你想获得更多的积分，还要降低速度，你应该组合。再次扣球后，
        无论你碰到哪个组合都会发生。如果任何球到达屏幕游戏的结束将结束。
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_ch">二合一</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_ch">用相同的颜色顺序触摸最少2个球</string>
    <string name="bonustext_ch">奖金</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_ch">一次在15次移动和移动颜色</string>

    //GERMANY
    <string name="gametext_al">SPIEL</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_al">Wenn Bälle kommen, können Sie jeden Ball in jedem berühren
        Position. Wenn du einen Ball berührst, bekommst du 10 Punkte, aber die Geschwindigkeit der Kugeln nimmt zu.
        Wenn du mehr Punkte bekommen willst und auch die Geschwindigkeit verringern solltest du Combos machen. Auch nach dem Pressen Bonusball,
        Egal welcher Ball Sie berühren Combo auftreten wird. Wenn irgendeine Kugel das Ende des Bildschirms erreicht, wird das Spiel vorbei sein.
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_al">COMBO</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_al">Berühre mindestens 2 Kugeln mit der gleichen Farbsequenz</string>
    <string name="bonustext_al">BONUS</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_al">Kommt einmal in 15 Züge und verschiebt Farbe</string>

    //SPAİN
    <string name="gametext_ıs">JUEGO</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_ıs"> Cuando las bolas están bajando, tú puedes tocar cualquier bola en cualquier posición
        Siempre que toques una bola, recibirás 10 puntos, pero la velocidad de las bolas aumentará. Si también quieres conseguir
        más puntos y hacer que la velocidad de las bolas disminuya, debes hacer combos. Tras presionar la bola de bonus, no importa
        que bola toques, el combo ocurriráSi cualquier bola alcanza el final de la pantalla de juego, el juego acabará
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_ıs">COMBO</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_ıs"> Toca como mínimo 2 bolas con la misma secuencia de color</string>
    <string name="bonustext_ıs">PRIMA</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_ıs">Aparece uno cada 15 movimientos y cambia de color</string>


    //JAPAN
    <string name="gametext_jp">ゲーム</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_jp">ボールが降りてくると、あなたはどんなボールにも触れることができます
        ポジション。あなたがボールに触れるたびにあなたは10ポイントを得るでしょうが、ボールのスピードは上がります。
        より多くのポイントを獲得し、速度を落としたい場合は、コンボを作成する必要があります。ボーナスボールを押した後も、
        どのボールをコンボに触れても問題は発生しません。ボールがスクリーンの終わりに達すると、ゲームは終了します。
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_jp">コンボ</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_jp">同じ色順の最低2つのボールをタッチする</string>
    <string name="bonustext_jp">ボーナス</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_jp">
1回15回の移動で色が変わります</string>

    //RUSSİAN
    <string name="gametext_rs">ИГРА</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_rs">Когда будут падать шары , вы можете коснуться любого шара в любом положении.
        Всякий раз, когда вы касаетесь мяча, вы получаете 10 очков, но скорость шаров будет  увеличиваться.
        Если вы хотите получить больше очков, а также уменьшить скорость, вы должны сделать комбо.
        Также после нажатия бонусного мяча, независимо от того, какого  вы коснетесь мяча, произойдет комбо.
        Если какой-либо мяч достигнет конца экрана игра будет окончена.
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_rs">комбо</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_rs">необходимо коснуться минимум 2х шаров с одинаковым цветом</string>
    <string name="bonustext_rs">БОНУС</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_rs">
Приходит один раз в 15 ходов.</string>

    //KOREAN
    <string name="gametext_kr">경기</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_kr">
공이 내려 오면 어떤 공을 건드릴 수 있습니다.
        위치. 당신이 공을 만질 때마다 당신은 10 점을 얻지 만 볼의 속도는 증가합니다.
        더 많은 포인트를 얻고 속도를 줄이려면 콤보를 만들어야합니다. 또한 보너스 공을 누른 후,
        콤보를 터치 한 공이 발생하더라도 상관 없습니다. 어떤 공이 화면 끝에 도달하면 게임은 종료됩니다.
    </string>
    <string name="combotext_kr">콤보</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_kr">
동일한 색상 순서로 최소 2 개의 볼을 터치하십시오.</string>
    <string name="bonustext_kr">보너스</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_kr">
1 회 15 회 이동 및 색상 이동</string>

    //ARABIC
    <string name="gametext_ar">لعبه</string>
    <string name="gameviewtext_ar">للعبة هي ان
        عند تحرك الطابتان الى الاسفل عليك بلمس ا
        حداهما عندما تلمس الطابة سوف تاخد 10 نقاط ولكن سرعة الطابة سوف تزداد
        عندما تصل الطابة نهاية الشاشة الللعبة تنتهي
        . اذا اردت ان تاخد المزيد من النقاط وتخفيض السرعة  يجب عمل مجموعان </string>
    <string name="combotext_ar">COMBO</string>
    <string name="comboviewtext_ar">المجموعة لمس طابتين من نفس اللون</string>
    <string name="bonustext_ar">علاوة</string>
    <string name="bonustextview_ar">ويأتي مرة واحدة في 15 التحركات والتحول اللون</string>


</resources>
